{
    "subject": "resource/Apache_Mesos",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/C++",
    "human_readable": "Apache Mesos is written in C++.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9515920877456665,
            "question": "Is Apache Mesos primarily developed using C++?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8124297857284546,
            "question": "What programming language is Apache Mesos written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5914962291717529,
            "question": "In what language was Apache Mesos originally developed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5715886950492859,
            "question": "Apache Mesos development primarily utilizes which coding language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5484508275985718,
            "question": "What programming language is commonly associated with Apache Mesos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48194438219070435,
            "question": "Can you tell me the language used for Apache Mesos development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4495515823364258,
            "question": "What is the primary programming language behind Apache Mesos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4103783667087555,
            "question": "What is the dominant programming language used for Apache Mesos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3912656009197235,
            "question": "Apache Mesos' codebase relies heavily on which language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3856528401374817,
            "question": "Which language powers the Apache Mesos framework?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Apache Mesos is written in C++.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8301_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Apache Mesos' codebase relies heavily on which language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8301_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the dominant programming language used for Apache Mesos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8301_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary programming language behind Apache Mesos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8301_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8301_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that \"Apache Mesos open source cluster manager is written in C++ programming language.\" and \"Yes, Apache Mesos open source cluster manager is written in C++ programming language.\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Apache Mesos open source cluster manager is written in C++ programming language,\" which supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}